Attacking another country's embassy is grounds for war, bar none, doesn't matter who you are.
If you didn't know better and you opened up the news app, you would think that Israel was bracing for an unprovoked attack from Iran.
NPR's classic, Both Sides, What About-ism, to Fox's full-blown xenophobia, hide in your bunker, the evil terrorists are coming.
And what they're leaving out is that on April 1st, an Israeli airstrike destroyed the Iranian consulate annex building adjacent to their embassy in Syria.
And that was Israel's whole point.
If they can force Iran to retaliate, then that forces the U.S. to get involved in the war, more so than just funding it.
White House sources say Biden is frustrated that he wasn't consulted on X, Y, and Z attack.
I'm sorry. Cry me a fucking river. They are emboldened in these actions, bombing Lebanon, bombing Syria, because you haven't put in any motion for accountability since the start of this.
Iran is backed into a corner. If they get involved, then suddenly it's a war with America as well.
If they don't, they're saying to the world, you can bomb our embassies, you can take out our top commanders in a foreign country with no repercussion.
What would you do if you were Iran?
What would you do if you're operating easily?
You would be I'm Unknown H